<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
 
 <title>Dan Hough</title>
 <link href="http://www.danielhough.co.uk/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="http://www.danielhough.co.uk/"/>
 <updated>2012-11-25T22:23:07+00:00</updated>
 <id>http://www.danielhough.co.uk/</id>
 <author>
   <name>Daniel Hough</name>
   <email>dan@danielhough.co.uk</email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>Dear Internet, Issue &#35;1</title>
   <link href="http://www.danielhough.co.uk/blog/Dear-Internet-Issue-1"/>
   <updated>2012-11-18T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
   <id>http://www.danielhough.co.uk/blog/Dear-Internet-Issue-1</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dear Internet&lt;/strong&gt;, Some years ago, I started writing music under the name &lt;strong&gt;Dan Plus Add&lt;/strong&gt;. Many asked questions such as &amp;#8220;Who the hell is Ad?&amp;#8221; or &amp;#8220;Where do you find your inspiration?&amp;#8221; or (a personal favourite of mine) &amp;#8220;Why are you crashing my wedding with your beaten-up acoustic guitar and an empty box of Oreo cookies filled with poorly-labelled CDs?&amp;#8221;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Well, Internet, I look back on those years fondly. I somehow managed to write two full albums, get one of them on Spotify, play about 6 gigs (I even was paid in beer for one of them!), sell £30 worth of digital-format music to you lovely people, and meet &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.superpowerless.co.uk/&quot;&gt;some&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://btype.tumblr.com/&quot;&gt;other&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://benforbes.com/&quot;&gt;like-minded&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.jonathancoulton.com/&quot;&gt;musicians&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Then, I &lt;strong&gt;stopped&lt;/strong&gt;. &lt;a href=&quot;http://huddle.com&quot;&gt;Work&lt;/a&gt; happened, Reddit distracted me and I generally lost my way a bit on the music front.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This blog post, and the website which goes with it, is the official indication that I am in fact, back in the game.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some people think it&amp;#8217;s a bit old-fashioned, Internet, for a musician to have an official website since there are so many places where I can set up a page. To those people I say, &amp;#8220;get off my lawn you young hooligans, I do what I want.&amp;#8221; Nevertheless, I have set up a &lt;a href=&quot;http://danplusadd.bandcamp.com&quot;&gt;bandcamp page&lt;/a&gt;, I have my second album, &lt;a href=&quot;http://open.spotify.com/album/2t5pxCYilQExlopyymFI2U&quot;&gt;Matters of Great Importance, on Spotify&lt;/a&gt; and obviously there&amp;#8217;s &lt;a href=&quot;http://twitter.com/danplusadd&quot;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.facebook.com/danplusadd&quot;&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt;. These links are useful, because it means I can spam you regardless of to which side of the epic &lt;strong&gt;Battle for the Internet&lt;/strong&gt; between all the sites &amp;#8211; which I definitely did not just make up right now &amp;#8211; you have pledged your alliegance. I&amp;#8217;m gonna update &lt;strong&gt;at least&lt;/strong&gt; Twitter and Facebook whenever I release a new song.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In conclusion, Internet, I missed you. So did my guitar. Watch this page for more. A new song is approaching.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Dan&lt;/p&gt;</content>
 </entry>
 
 
</feed>